（ビートボックスの音）
Yeah
Yo, you heard?
Demons be real, that's the word
（ワム）♪なぁ 聞いたか
いるらしいぜ 悪魔が
Over here, out there
Demons be lurkin' everywhere
そりゃもう そこらじゅう
いるみたいだ悪魔が
What form is they takin'?
Tell me how they look,
だけど実際
悪魔ってどんな見かけ？
姿 形 振る舞いまで
なんも俺はしらねぇ
Hell if I know, but they got me shook,
They demons, so they evil,
（ガビ）
♪そりゃ当然 悪(わ)りーさ
Demons is as demons do
なんせ 悪魔だしな
Make them ugly grills illegal,
Demons is as demons do
見た目も
きっとオゾマシイ
なんせ 悪魔だしな
盗む　犯す　奪う　殺す
Steal, destroy, murder, spy,
no rules apply
きっと全部あり
Stackin' paper by dirty deeds,
Where you and I can't see
誰も知らねーとこで
きたねー 手口使い make money
But look, tons of people in the world,
already doin' that, actually
（ワム）
♪だけど そんな奴は普通
そこらじゅうに
みろよごまんと
いるじゃねーか 実際
So what's the dilly up in here?
どうなってんだ 一体
You and demons, demons and I,
How we gonna draw dat fine line?
お前と悪魔 俺と悪魔
どこにあんだ 違い
見分けられる奴なんて
Don't nobody nowhere,
Know the difference no more
そりゃもうどこもいない
（バボ）♪俺は違う 絶対
悪魔なんてならない
Not you, not me
-But I ain't gonna be no demon
-You sure?
（バボ）♪俺は違う 絶対
悪魔なんてならない
（ワム）♪本当か
-You a demon?
-Hell no
（ワム）♪本当か
お前は悪魔か？
それも俺は知らない
（ワム）♪ちげーよ
Yeah, you say that, but I don't know
I only know me, and how I roll
お前は悪魔か？
それも俺は知らない
俺にわかることは
俺がどんな奴か それだけ
Not out to please peeps,
Just out to protect me
お人好しはごめんだ
自分の身守るのは俺だけ
Mess around,
Might get shanked from the back
突然 後ろから
刺されちまう かもな
Let that guard down,
Might get took for all your bank
油断したら
身ぐるみ 奪われちまう
あとは 殺されるのは
いつも弱い奴
The cullin' of the weak,
Shit ain't never gonna change
それは変わらねー
The cullin' of the weak,
Shit ain't never gonna change
殺されるのはいつも弱い奴
それは変わらねー
The ones that get shook,
Get guns and hit the streets
（ワム）♪ビビッちまった奴から
武器を持って人殺し
But most ain't shook,
And ain't packin' no heat
ビビらない丸腰は
逆にそれが命取り
Last mistake they'll ever make,
'Cuz with guns at stake
まともじゃない奴から
順に武器をとってく
The first to grab are the worst of us
まともな 奴から
また順に殺されていく
Shots pop off,
The first to die are the best of us
誰が味方 誰が敵か
誰もわからないまま
Nobody knows friend from foe
試されてる
人が人でいる ためのあり方
Gettin' tested as we should
To stay human fo' sho'
Needle o' truth
Haystack o' doubt
疑心暗鬼　暗中模索
始まる負の連鎖
Chain reaction goes blaow!
Needle o' truth
Haystack o' doubt
疑心暗鬼　暗中模索
始まる負の連鎖
Chain reaction goes blaow!
WEAK HUMANS,
WISE DEMONS
（飛鳥(あすか) 了(りょう)）確かに悪魔は
我々 人間より強力です
Make no mistake,
demons are stronger than humans.
However, humans have survived
many times before
しかし人類は これまでにも―
in the face of
physically superior enemies.
肉体的に優れた敵との
生存競争を―
幾多も打ち勝ち
生き抜いてきました
I have no doubt the war against demonkind
今回の悪魔との戦いも―
必ずや勝利を収めるでしょう
will see humanity triumph again!
Wooo, Ryo!
（白シャツ隊１）いいぞ 了！
（人々の歓声）
（白シャツ隊２）人類万歳！
Humans forever!
（人々の歓声）
（白シャツ隊３）悪魔撃退！
Death to all demons!
You can't fool me!
You're all demons!
（男）だまされないぞ！
お前ら みんな悪魔なんだろ！
分かってるぞ！
I know it!
人間はもういないんだ！
ハッハッハッハ…
There are no humans anymore!
No.
（不動(ふどう) 明(あきら)）違う
こんなはずじゃなかった
It wasn't supposed to be like this.
&lrm;
んっ
（着信音）
了 俺はさっき
殺される人間を見た
Ryo, I just saw someone get killed.
そうか
I see.
人間だ
He was a human.
ラリってたが 悪魔じゃなかった
He was crazy, but he wasn't a demon.
そうか
I see.
（明）お前 どうして
そんなに冷静なんだ
Ryo,
how are you so calm?
こうしてる間にも―
Tons of people who aren't demons
are dying right now.
悪魔じゃない人間が
大勢死んでるんだぞ！
悪魔もいくらかは死んでいる
Some demons have died, too.
（明）あっ…
明 これは人間と悪魔の戦争だ
Akira.
This is a war between demons and humans.
死人くらい出る
-And every war has casualties.
-You knew this would happen?
お前 まさか こうなること…
This amount of sacrifice is unavoidable.
（了）
このくらいの犠牲はしょうがない
悪魔でないことを証明するのは
時間や手間もかかる
It takes time and effort
to prove someone isn't a demon.
What's going to change by you going around
and saving one or two people?
１日動き回って
お前が１人 ２人助けてどうなる？
The big picture stays the same.
Leave it to the government.
大局は変わらない
政府に任せておくんだ
Are you saying just
stand by and do nothing?
（明）何もせずに見てろだと？
-It's a necessary evil.
-Ryo!
必要悪だ
了！ てめえに
人間の血が流れてるなら―
You can't say that
if there's human blood in your veins.
言えねえセリフだ！
（了）俺が考えていたより
人間は脆弱(ぜいじゃく)だったということだ
It just means humans are more vulnerable
than I thought they were.
多少の犠牲は しかたがない
Some sacrifice is inevitable.
（明）しかたなくなんかねえ！
No, it's not!
（不通話音）
（羽音）
（着地する音）
じっとしてろと言ったろ
おら！
I told you to stay put. Here.
（幸田(こうだ)燃寛(もゆる)）おっと
How long do I have to hide out
in a tiny place like this?
いつまで こんな狭(せめ)えとこに
隠れてなきゃならねえんだ？
（明）下はひどい状況だ
It's a mess down there.
Everyone knows your face.
You'd get hunted down right away.
お前は顔が売れてるから
すぐに狩られちまうぞ
It's your fault
everyone knows what I am now.
正体バレてんのは
てめえらのせいだろうが
あむ…
デビルマンは
俺たち以外にもきっといる
There must be other Devilmen besides us.
２人っきりじゃキモすぎる
Kill me if it's just the two of us.
（明）ここに
もっと連れてきても住めるか？
If I bring more, think we can live here?
ここより
あっちのほうが広そうだぜ
That place looks bigger than here.
But it attracts too much attention.
（明）あそこは目立ってまずい
ここは狭すぎて
アスリートには息がつまらあ
This place isn't even big enough
for me to stretch my legs.
But if it's just to sleep,
I can stay here till whenever.
けど寝泊まりだけなら
いくらでも大丈夫だぜ
Even though the elevator doesn't work.
エレベーター 使えねえけどな
すまん　頼む
Sorry. Thanks.
"And one of them with Jesus stretched out
his hand, and drew his sword,
（牧村(まきむら)ノエル）すると―
イエスに従事していた者の１人が
剣を抜き―
大祭司の下僕に襲いかかり
その耳を切り落とした
and struck a servant of the high priest's,
and smote off his ear.
その時 イエスは彼に言われた
Then said Jesus unto him,
put up again thy sword into his place,
“剣を鞘(さや)に納めなさい”
for all they that take the sword
shall perish with the sword."
“剣を抜く者は
皆 剣により滅びます”
（牧村太郎(たろう)）
それって戦っちゃダメってこと？
Does that mean we shouldn't fight?
そうだ
That's right. If swords are crossed,
life will always be sacrificed.
互いが剣を合わせれば
必ず犠牲が出る
じゃあ どうすればいいの？
So what are we supposed to do?
（足音）
Love. We use love.
（牧村美樹(みき)）愛だよ 愛
（太郎）わあっ
Is that strong?
それ 強いの？
強い強い
世界で一番強いんだから
It's strong.
強い強い
世界で一番強いんだから
（太郎）うう…
It's the strongest thing in the world.
ふふふふ
-No! Stop it!
-Take that.
ふふふふ
（太郎）やだ！
やめてよ んんん…
ほ～ら ふふふふ
This huge love will wrap you up, Taro.
（太郎のうめき声）
大きな愛が
太郎を包みこんじゃうぞ
Quit it!
ふふふふ…
（太郎）やだってば！ もう…
Cut it out. Jeez.
（ターコの鳴き声）
（陸上部員１）人 減ったね
There's a lot less people now.
（陸上部員２）
部活どころじゃないしね
It's no time to come to track.
（陸上部員１）
ミーコなんて学校も来ないし
Miko hasn't even been to school.
（陸上部員２）いいよ　あいつ
速くなってから感じ悪かったし
Who cares? She's been stuck up
ever since she got faster.
（陸上部員２）いいよ　あいつ
速くなってから感じ悪かったし
（美樹）それ！
ふふふ… ナイス！
（陸上部員１）
美樹も犬には勝てないか
Looks like Miki can't even beat a dog.
I feel like running's pointless now.
（陸上部員２）
走るの 意味ない気してきた
（犬とたわむれる
美樹の声）
そもそも人間
走るようにできてないんだよ
Humans aren't made
for running to begin with.
Then how about demons?
（美樹）それ！
（陸上部員１）じゃあ悪魔は？
（陸上部員２）飛ぶんじゃない？
Maybe they fly.
（陸上部員１･２）ふふふ…
（陸上部員１）そっか
I guess.
（犬）クンクン…
（美樹）えへへ
（美樹）“人を蔑むのは簡単”
It's easy
to give people the cold shoulder.
“でも理解するのはとても難しい”
But it's really hard to understand them.
Sometimes you'll even find a new side
to family you've known for years.
〝長年連れ添った家族でも
時に新しい面を見せる〞
No matter how hard you hope,
〝どれだけ思っても
生涯誰一人―〞
it's sad to think about
not understanding anyone your entire life.
〝理解できないかもと
思うと―〞
〝とても寂しい〞
〝でも理解したい〞
But I want to understand.
〝粘り強く
理解したいと願う〞
I pray I want to keep understanding.
I'll find the courage to believe.
“信じる勇気を持って…”
WHY IS SHE PREACHING?
PATHETIC.
STOP PRETENDING TO BE A GOOD GIRL.
（ミーコ）はあ… はあ… はあ…
（ホームレスの男）姉ちゃん
色っぽい息遣いだねえ
Hey, girl.
The way you breathe sure is sexy.
今度は俺といい汗かこうよ
Want to work up a good sweat with me next?
（ホームレスの男）はあ はあ はあ
はあ はあ はあ…
Just like that.
うっ おっ いい… いいっ…！
I'm gonna come.
（ハエの羽音）
（ミーコ）もういいよね
It's been long enough, right?
おばあちゃんの自慢の風景も
ちょっと飽きた
I'm kinda tired
of my grandma's special view.
（白シャツ隊１）おい 待て！
（美樹）んっ…
Hey, wait.
（白シャツ隊１）
女１人で出歩くとは おかしいな
It's odd for a girl to be
walking around on her own.
男はたむろって歩くのが普通なの？
Is it normal for guys
to hang out and walk around?
（白シャツ隊１）
あーん？ その目 外人か？
Those eyes. You a foreigner?
（白シャツ隊２）
こいつ 牧村美樹だぜ
She's Miki Makimura.
（白シャツ隊２）
陸上界の魔女　ハーフだよ
The witch of the track. She's a mix.
（美樹）ちょっ…
（白シャツ隊１）ちょっと来い
-Hey.
-Come with us. We need to check you out.
取り調べてやる
んっ… 放せ！
Let me go!
（美樹）放して！
（子供たち）外人！ 外人！
Foreigner! Foreigner!
（明）ダメ！
Stop it!
（子供）何だ こいつ？
男のくせに泣きやがって！
What the hell?
Look, he's crying like a little girl.
Cut it out!
ダメ！
（子供）なんでえ バカが
What an idiot.
（子供たち）あははは…
（明）美樹ちゃん 危ない時―
Miki,
I'll be there whenever you're in trouble.
僕がいるから
（白シャツ隊１）
人一倍足が速(はえ)えのも―
Maybe you can run so fast
because you're a demon.
悪魔だからじゃねえか？
（白シャツ隊３）
日本をバカにしやがって！
This is for Japan!
Help! Akira!
（美樹）やばいよ　明くん！
Akira.
（美樹）明…
（ワム）また会ったな
So, we meet again.
（白シャツ隊３）
こいつ… おおっ！
You.
You're on her side?
（白シャツ隊１）
味方する… ぐふっ…
Stop bullying the weak
and go get the demons.
（ガビ）弱い者(もん)イジメしてねえで
悪魔取り締まれよ！
（呼び笛）
あらら たくさん来た
Uh-oh. Here comes more.
逃げよ！
Let's run.
（ガビ）えっ ちょっと待て！
Hey, wait a sec.
（ワム）さすが魔女
速(はえ)えんだな
No wonder they call you a witch.
You're fast.
（美樹）そっちこそ強いんだね
You, too. You're strong.
（ガビ）弱(よえ)えと損するからな
自分くれえ守れねえと
Being weak gets you in trouble.
You need to be able to protect yourself.
女が一人歩きなんて
あの人魚どうした？
A girl walking all alone...
Where's your mermaid?
（美樹）ん？
不動 明くん！
That's Akira Fudo.
Remember his name.
名前 覚えといてよ
（武装警官）出てこい！ 悪魔だ！
There! It's a demon!
Close off the roads!
周辺道路を封鎖しろ！
（サイレン）
ひるむな！ 撃て 撃て！
Don't hold back! Shoot it!
Fall back. The flamethrower's here.
（サイレン）
下がれ！ 火炎が来たぞ
（デビルマン）こ… これは！
Is this--?
Die, you demon!
（人々の叫び声）
Eat that!
（人々の歓声）
Kill that thing!
Kill it!
Die, demon!
（隊長）逃がすな！
-Don't let it escape!
-Burn it! Do it!
（デーモン）ぐおおお…
You're not a demon.
You're a Devilman, aren't you?
（デビルマン）
君は悪魔じゃないな？
デビルマンだろう？
大丈夫だ　俺と来い
It's okay. Come with me.
I'm also a Devilman, too.
I have a human heart.
俺も人間の心を持った
デビルマンなんだ
よせ！ 俺は味方だ！
Stop! I'm on your side!
（隊長）撃て！
Shoot!
（銃声）
Stop!
やめ！
（デビルマン）うおおお～～っ
（隊長）もう１体 確認！
There's another one!
Launch to the upper right!
右上 撃て！
なぜ見境なく殺す！
Why are you killing like this?
Why?!
なぜ！？
なっ… 誰だ？
Who is it? I know you're there.
いるのは分かってるぞ
あんた… 生きてたの？
You're alive?
You were in the 4-by-100 relay.
お前 ４継の…
見られたからには！
Since you already saw me...
うっ う…
（ミーコ）はあ… はあ…
お互い…
Now you see me.
（幸田）悪魔ってか
A fellow demon.
The current circumstances
are in our favor.
（ノン）
状況は我ら優位に働いている
（ゼン）米軍のほうはどうだ？
-How are things with the U.S. military?
-We already control them.
（ヌガ）すでに我々の管理下にある
人間を滅ぼすのに十分な兵器量だ
There are enough of them
to destroy the human race.
Can we not mass-produce weapons...
（議員１）国民全員が
携帯できるよう―
DEMON COUNCIL
武器を大量生産することは
できんのか？
-...and arm the public with them?
-We can't legislate it in time.
法整備は間に合わん
Beyond that,
there are too many cases
（議員２）それより―
民間人が民間人を
殺害している事件のほうが―
where civilians murdering other civilians.
多すぎますよ
（議員３）政府が徹底的に―
The government must exterminate
this problem at the root.
根こそぎやっちまわなきゃ
ダメなんだ
徴兵したらどうなんだ
今なら文句出ないだろ
What about a military draft?
People won't complain if we do it now.
We must be mindful
of our neighboring nations.
（議員４）隣国の動きも
気をつけなければいけない
隣国はすでに
悪魔の手に落ちたという情報もある
Intel suggests they've already
been overrun by the demons.
（議員５）どういう情報ですか？
根拠をおっしゃってください
Where does that intel come from?
What is it based on?
Rather than immigrating humans,
（議員１）人間の入国検査より
貨物のほうが危ないんじゃないか？
maybe cargo is more dangerous.
（了）これは悪魔どもの思うつぼだ
They're falling for the demons' trap.
（美樹）入って
お茶くらい出すから
Come in. I'll pour some tea for you.
（ワム）へ～ いいうちだな
（美樹）ありがと
Sweet. Nice place.
Thanks.
（ノエル）
美樹！ これを見てくれ
Miki. Look at this.
（美樹）はっ…！
ANTI-DEMON
DEMON-CONTROL
DEMON-REPELLENT SPRAY
（太郎）はあ… はあ…
What's wrong?
（牧村亜樹子(あきこ)）どうしたの？
（太郎）あっ…
（亜樹子）大丈夫
悪魔が来ても お母さんいるから
It's all right.
I won't let any demons get you.
（ママ友１）牧村さん！
Mrs. Makimura.
聞いた？
大谷(おおたに)さんとこのサオリちゃん…
Did you hear about Saori Otani?
She was a demon.
（ママ友２）悪魔だったのよ
What? Saori?
（亜樹子）
えっ？ サオリちゃんが？
（ママ友１）大谷さんも
警察に連れていかれたの
The police took Mrs. Otani, too.
親も悪魔じゃないかって…
（亜樹子）そんな…
-They think the parents might be demons.
-That can't be.
（ママ友２）でも実の娘が
悪魔なのに気づかないなんてある？
But how could she not have noticed
her own daughter was a demon?
Oh, she knew, alright.
She just didn't say anything.
（ママ友１）知ってたのよ
知ってて黙ってたのよ
（ママ友２）悪質！
That's horrific.
That means my child was associating
with a demon?
うちの子も悪魔と
つきあってたってことでしょ？
怖いわ
How terrifying.
えっ！？
Taro?
太郎ちゃん？
太郎ちゃん！ 返事して
太郎ちゃーん！
Taro! Answer right now!
Taro!
（太郎）お母さん…
Mom.
（亜樹子）急にいなくなっちゃうと
びっくりするでしょ？
Don't disappear like that. You scared me.
ごめんなさい お母さん
I'm sorry, Mom.
That's all right. Next time...
いいのよ　今度から… はっ！
（荷物を落とす音）
（太郎）ごめんなさい　僕 お肉…
I'm sorry. I wanted meat.
お肉 我慢できない
I couldn't help myself.
（亜樹子）ああああ…
DEMONS RELATIVE TO POPULATION
（扉が開く音）
話がある
We need to talk.
明 世の中は変わってしまった
Akira. The world has changed.
戦慄の時代が始まったんだ
An age of horror has begun.
Humans are being made
to dance the dance of deadly hell.
人間が踊らされる死の地獄踊りだ
我々は悪魔の存在を明らかにした
We exposed the existence of demons.
But we've opened Pandora's box
at the same time.
しかし同時に
パンドラの箱を開けてしまったんだ
人間は怖がる…
人間は怖いんだよ…
Humans get scared.
Humans are scared.
分かるか？ 人間は弱いんだ
Don't you see? Humans are weak.
What do you think will come of a humanity
悪魔の存在を知り―
恐怖を煽られた人間は
どうなると思う？
terrified by the discovery
of demons' existence?
Demons are strong and cunning.
They will bide their time patiently.
悪魔は強く狡猾(こうかつ)だ
今は静観している
They are calmly watching
as humans doubt and kill each other.
疑い合い 殺し合う人間を
冷静に見ているんだ
Humans have the courage to
conquer fear and fight.
人間には
恐怖を抑えて戦う勇気がある！
They have intelligence. Powerful armies.
知力がある！
巨大な武力もだ！
悪魔と戦えるはずだ！
They can fight the demons.
ふふふ… だといいが…
Let's hope so.
But millions of humans
are being sacrificed
数百頭の悪魔を殺すため
数千万の人間が犠牲になっている
to kill just a few hundred demons.
The weapons that are supposed to protect
humans are helping to destroy them.
人間を守るための兵器が
人間を滅ぼすために一役買うんだ
疑心暗鬼にかられた人間どもが
とんでもないことをやり始めるぞ！
Humans that get lost in their suspicions
will start doing terrible things.
もうお前１人の力では
どうにもならない
There's nothing you can do
with your own power alone.
ここは静かにしているべきだ
You should keep quiet.
デビルマンの敵が悪魔だけなら
まだいい
Things would be better
if your only enemies
しかし！
were demons, but the Devilman himself
is a demon from a human point of view.
人間からすれば
デビルマンも悪魔のうちだ！
あ…
This is the biggest show in history!
The war is starting.
史上最大のショーだ！
戦争が始まるんだ！
A war against a form of life
人類がかつて経験したことのない
異生物との戦争だ！
unknown to human experience!
What can you accomplish fighting alone?
１人で戦って何ができる！
Don't get overconfident.
うぬぼれるな！
今は身を潜めて見守るんだ！
You should keep yourself hidden
and observe the future of humanity.
人類の行く末を！
お前が１体２体 倒したところで
大局に影響はない
Killing one or two demons
means nothing
in the grand scheme of things.
人間は自滅する…
１人残らず死に絶える
Humanity will self-destruct.
Every single one of them will die.
Humans won't self-destruct.
人間は自滅しない！
デビルマンは１人じゃない
I'm not the only Devilman.
他にも 悪魔に打ち勝った
心を持った人間はいるんだ！
There are others with human hearts
who defeated their demons.
We shouldn't be apart.
I'm going to gather the Devilmen.
バラバラになってはダメだ
俺はデビルマンを集める！
集めて悪魔たちと戦う！
-Together we'll fight the demons.
-No.
やめろ！
俺は そんなことのために―
That's not why I made you a Devilman.
お前を
デビルマンにしたんじゃない！
はっ…
（明）これまでだ 了
It's over, Ryo.
ちょっと待て 明！
Wait, Akira.
どけ！ 了！
Get out of my way, Ryo!
It backfired.
裏目に出やがった
明 頼むから生きのびてくれ
Akira.
Please, stay alive.
The Revelation...
黙示録…
The god of demons, Satan,
lost his body in the war with the Lord.
“神との戦いにより
体を失いし悪魔神サタン”
“永劫(えいごう)の時を経て無より蘇り―”
After an eternity, he rose from nothing
“悪魔軍団を率いて
天空より災いをなす”
and led a demon army
that brought hell from the sky.
Yet the army of God
defeated them once more.
“神の軍団再びこれを撃つ”
神の軍団… サタン？
The army of God?
Satan?
（明）ただいまー
I'm back.
（美樹）明くん！ これ！
Akira, look at this!
Noel, thank you for everything.
（亜樹子）〝ノエル
今まで ありがとう〞
〝あなたと一緒に暮らせて
とても幸せでした〞
“太郎を連れてゆきます”
I'm taking Taro and leaving.
I love you.
“あなたを愛してる”
And Miki and Taro and Akira, too.
“美樹も 太郎も 明くんも…”
I'm glad we were able
to be a happy family.
“幸せな家族でいられて
よかった”
“連れ添う約束
果たせなくて ごめんなさい”
I'm sorry I can't fulfill my promise.
“美樹をよろしくお願いします”
I leave Miki in your hands.
MIKI, I'M SORRY AS A MOTHER.
LOOK AFTER DAD.
LOVE, MOM
おばさんが出ていった？
Your mom left?
（美樹）太郎も一緒なの
Taro is with her, too.
（ノエル）捜してくる
（美樹）私も！
-I'll go look for them.
-Me, too.
（ノエル）ダメだ！
No, stay.
Someone needs to be here for her
もし ふいに母さんが戻ってきたら
おかえりを言う人間が必要だ
in case she comes back.
明くん 美樹を頼む
Akira, look after Miki.
You have my word.
はい 任せてください
You've changed.
You're not the old Akira.
変わったな　あの明くんがな…
Uncle.
（明）おじさん
Be careful.
気をつけて
大丈夫
神様が守ってくださるよ
I'll be all right. God will watch over me.
（警告音）
（アナウンサー）緊急速報です
Breaking news.
The president of the United States just
先ほど合衆国大統領より
非常事態宣言が発令されました
declared a state of national emergency.
アメリカ国防省は
今回の悪魔について―
The Department of National Defense
closed borders
ロシアの生物兵器の疑いが
強まったとみて国境を封鎖
in the wake of suspicions that
the demons are a Russian bioweapon.
The Seventh Fleet has been dispatched
すでに第７艦隊が出撃しており―
追ってＮＡＴＯ軍全体の展開も
進められるもようです
and orders are underway
to deploy all NATO forces.
（士官）戦闘になるのでしょうか？
Will it come to combat?
（将軍）核を撃ち合えば―
If both sides launch nuclear weapons,
we'll all die, not just the demons.
悪魔だけではなく
我々も滅んでしまう
それくらい
相手も分かっているはずですよね
They must realize that, too, no?
（何か突き刺さる音）
（将軍）そうだな　だから…
They certainly do. Which is why...
こちらから しかけてやる
we're going to launch our own attack.
あ… く…
戦術核を使用する！
パーティーの始まりだ！
We'll use the tactical nuclear weapon.
Let's get this party started!
（デーモンたち）イエッサー
Yes, sir!
（ミサイル発射音）
何だ？
What's going on?
What's that?
（デーモン）何だ この光！？
The men of Sodom, compassed
the house round, and called unto Lot,
（神父）“ソドムの人々が
ロトの家を囲み 言った”
"Where are the men which
came in to thee this night?"
“今夜 お前たちの所に
来た者たちを―”
“ここに出しなさい”
“彼らはロトに激しく迫り
戸を破ろうとした”
And they pressed sore upon Lot,
and came near to break the door.
“主は彼らの行いを見て
この町を滅ぼすことに決めた”
Alas, the Lord saw their deeds,
and in his judgment
resolved to overthrow those cities.
“この時 ロトの妻が―”
Then, against the will of the Lord,
（パイロット）うわあ
“神の使いとの約束に
背いたので―”
his wife looked back from behind him,
and she became a pillar of salt.
“神の使いとの約束に
背いたので―”
“塩の柱になった”
“主は 硫黄と火とを
主の所 すなわち―”
Then the Lord rained upon Sodom
and upon Gomorrah brimstone and fire
“天から ソドムとゴモラの
上に降らせて―”
from the Lord out of heaven.
“その町々の全ての住民と
その地に生えている物を―”
And he overthrew those cities,
and all the plain,
and that which grew upon the ground.
“ことごとく滅ぼされた”
（アナウンサー）ご覧ください
Look at this.
It's an image taken
from the satellite track.
これが
衛星軌道から撮影された画像です
（ゼン）これは…！
-My God...
-The light's diameter...
（アナウンサー）
この光の直径は―
is more than 10,000 km
and at present...
１万キロにも及ぶと推測され
現在その…
（了）ああああ…
ぎゃああああああ
ひいい！ あああああ…
&lrm;
Subtitles by
Kristine Kenmochi